Finding Aid for the Fremont Ackerman Papers LSC.0312
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Huntington Park--Second addition--Irvington Avenue & Regent Street, Los Angeles County., 1906.; 2 items. (Box 110)
- Hyperion Avenue / Mildred Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1920.; 1 item. (Box 78)
- Independence Tract (G.B. Hill)--28th Street & 29th Street, Los Angeles County (?)., 2 items. (Box 116)
- Independence Tract--Compton Avenue & 29th Street, Los Angeles County., 1904.; 1 item. (Box 116)
- Industrial Center Tract--Palmetto Street & Alameda Street, Los Angeles County., 1907.; 2 items. (Box 115)
- Inglewood, Los Angeles County., 1888-1907.; 22 items. (Box 94)
- Inglewood--Block 101 maps--Railroad Street & Damask Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1907.; 2 items. (Box 115)
- Irrigation Map of Central California, California., 1922.; 1 item. (Box 150)
- Jefferson Street Park Tract--Jefferson & Fourth Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1906.; 1 item. (Box 121)
- Jefferson Street Park Tracts, Los Angeles., 1909.; 3 items. (Box 67)
- Kathryn Coit Tract--San Pasqual Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1914.; 2 items. (Box 108)
- Kensington Place--Western Avenue & 6th Street, Los Angeles., 1920.; 1 item. (Box 139)
- Kensington Place--Wilshire Boulevard & Western Avenue, Los Angeles., 1906.; 1 item. (Box 128)
- Kercheval Tract--Santa Clara Street & Alamo Street, Los Angeles County., 1887.; 1 item. (Box 116)
- Kuhrits Subdivision--Vernon Avenue & San Pedro Street, Los Angeles County., 1904.; 1 item. (Box 116)
- La Paloma Dr. & Los Amigos Street, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 5 items. (Box 101)
- Lankershim Tract--Tujunga Avenue & Weddington Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1910.; 4 items. (Box 128)
- Laughlin Park (folder 1 of 2), Los Angeles., 1913.; 15 items. (Box 72)
- Laughlin Park (folder 2 of 2), Los Angeles., 1913-1928.; 21 items. (Box 73)
- Laughlin Park (Tract 2099)--Franklin Avenue & Harvard Boulevard Hollywood., 1913.; 3 items. (Box 121)
- Lehosky Tract--Washington Street & Caroline Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1922.; 10 items. (Box 123)
- Letts (Arthur) property--Franklin Avenue & Edgmont Street, Hollywood., 1922.; 3 items. (Box 120)
- Lick Tract--Los Feliz Boulevard & Vermont Avenue, Los Angeles., 1920.; 2 items. (Box 113)
- Lincoln Tract (Mansfield)--Santa Monica / Lemona Avenue, Los Angeles., n.d.; 3 items. (Box 156)
- Lincoln Tract--Warner Avenue & Santa Monica Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1905.; 9 items. (Box 109)
- Loew (Mr.) & Wolff (Ralph G.) Property--San Vincente Road, Los Angeles County., 1923.; 1 item. (Box 124)
- Lone * Tract (Clark & Bryan)--Pico / Hoover, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Los Angeles (Map of Territory Annexed), Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Los Angeles--administrative center, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Los Angeles--plan of city government, Los Angeles., 1931.; 2 items. (Box 148)
- Los Angeles and adjoining cities map published by Security Trust & Savings Bank, Los Angeles County., 1928.; 1 item. (Box 153)
- Los Angeles and vicinity map published by Security First National Bank, Los Angeles County., 1930.; 1 item. (Box 153)
- Los Angeles County, Los Angeles County., 1923.; 2 items. (Box 157)
- Los Angeles County & Orange County, California., 1920.; 1 item. (Box 149)
- Los Angeles map published by Citizens National Bank, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 153)
- Los Angeles River and it's destruction of Frank F. Snell's Land, Los Angeles County., 1915.; 1 item. (Box 137)
- Los Angeles Street / O.W. Childs estate, Los Angeles., 1912.; 7 items. (Box 71)
- Los Feliz / Vermont / Franklin / Edgemont, Los Angeles., 1920.; 1 item. (Box 79)
- Los Feliz Boulevard / Cummings, Los Angeles., 1926-1938.; 16 items. (Box 80)
- Los Feliz Boulevard / Edgemont Street, Los Angeles County., 1921.; 1 item. (Box 80)
- Los Feliz Heights (Cook-Woodley & Thompson)--Plat no.2--Tract no.3733, Los Angeles., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 156)
- Los Nietos & La Mirada Road, Los Angeles County., 1907.; 2 items. (Box 131)
- Loyola Tract--Eagle Rock Avenue & Edgar Avenue, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 117)
- Lynch & Wrights's Land--Part of La Puente Ranch, Los Angeles County., 1904.; 1 item. (Box 136)
- Mac Kay Tract--San Fernando Street & Arvia Street, Los Angeles County., 1906.; 2 items. (Box 115)
- Maclay Colony of San Fernando, Los Angeles County., 1 item. (Box 156)
- Maie Avenue Profile--Florence Avenue to Nadeau Street, Los Angeles County., 1923.; 1 item. (Box 132)
- Main Street / Slauson, Los Angeles., 1911.; 3 items. (Box 71)
- Main Street Boulevard Tract (Bowen & Chamberlin), Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Main Street Boulevard Tract (Bowen & Chamberlin)--Marshall Street & Main, Los Angeles County., 1904.; 2 items. (Box 110)
- Main Street Boulevard Tract--Main Street & 52nd Street, Los Angeles., 1905.; 2 items. (Box 125)
- Main St., Moneta Avenue & Figueroa Street Tract, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 153)
- Malibu Encinal Beach, Los Angeles County., 1928, 1937.; 12 items. (Box 101)
- Maltman (John) property--Maltman Avenue & Carnation Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1906.; 1 item. (Box 124)
- Manhattan Beach subdivision--The Strand & Center Street, Los Angeles County., 1904.; 6 items. (Box 137)
- Mansfield Tract--Brooklyn Avenue & Sloat Street, Los Angeles., 1904.; 1 item. (Box 125)
- Mathews Street Extention--southward to Hollenbeck, Los Angeles., 1927.; 1 item. (Box 134)
- McCollum Street / Montana Street, Los Angeles County., 1923.; 1 item. (Box 82)
- McComb's South West Tract--Santa Monica Avenue & Western Avenue, Los Angeles., 1904.; 1 item. (Box 125)
- Melrose Park, Hancock Park, Wilshire Country Club & other properties, Los Angeles., 1932.; 1 item. (Box 149)
- Menlo Avenue & Hoover Street profile--132nd Street to 133th Street, Los Angeles., 1930.; 1 item. (Box 132)
- Menlo Park--Washington / Adams, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Menlo Park Subdivision no.3--Central Avenue & Washington Street, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 114)
- Mettler's Main Street & South Park Tract--Main Street & 61st Street, Los Angeles., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 156)
- Mettler's Main Street South Park Tract--Main Street & 61st Street, Los Angeles County., 1905.; 1 item. (Box 124)
- Micheltorena Street / Landa Street, Los Angeles County., 1923.; 5 items. (Box 83)
- Mid Pacific Railroad map of Nevada and a portion of California, Nevada & California., 1933.; 1 item. (Box 150)
- Midland Acres--Morton Avenue & Central Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1919.; 7 items. (Box 115)
- Midland Town Site, Los Angeles County., 1914.; 2 items. (Box 137)
- Miller & Holsinger addition--Vermont Avenue & Francis Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1905.; 1 item. (Box 116)
- Mills Tract--Winston Street, Los Angeles County., 1915.; 1 item. (Box 108)
- Mines Avenue and 9th Street profile--at Junction with Lorena Street, Los Angeles., 1934.; 1 item. (Box 133)
- Mining maps--miscellaneous, California, Colorado., 1897, 1929.; 9 items. (Box 105)
- Minnehaha Tract--Fawn Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1905.; 1 item. (Box 116)
- Mission Dr, Los Angeles County., 1921.; 1 item. (Box 78)
- Mitchell Block--Brooklyn Avenue & State Street, Los Angeles County., 1897.; 1 item. (Box 114)
- Moll (Mary P.) lot--Sunset Boulevard & Alpine Dr, Beverly Hills., 1926.; 2 items. (Box 110)
- Moneta Avenue & Apollo Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1917.; 1 item. (Box 77)
- Moneta Avenue & Laconia Boulevard, Los Angeles County., 1917.; 2 items. (Box 77)
- Moneta Place--Moneta Avenue / Bartol Street, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Montebello--Whittier Avenue & Poplar Avenue, Los Angeles., 1918.; 3 items. (Box 136)
- Monteleone Tract & Gunn (Alexander) Tract--Old River School Road, Los Angeles County., 1923.; 2 items. (Box 126)
- Monteleone Tract--Old River School Road, Los Angeles County., 1904.; 2 items. (Box 126)
- Montesano Tract--Benefit Street & Fairmont Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1907.; 1 item. (Box 115)
- Morningside Park--East Colorado Street & San Gabriel Boulevard Pasadena., 1940.; 1 item. (Box 121)
- Morton Rd.--Wright Road & Michigan Avenue, Los Angeles., 1921-1922.; 3 items. (Box 131)
- Morton Scott Tract--Echo Park Road & Effie Street, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 136)
- Mount Angeles Tract Park--Ave. 61 & Piedmont Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1907.; 6 items. (Box 118)
- Nadeau Orange Tract--partial map--Jefferson Street & Eureka Street, Los Angeles County., 1896.; 1 item. (Box 113)
- Nadeau Orange Tract Peremptory Sale--Central Avenue & Jefferson, Los Angeles., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 156)
- Nadeau Park Tract--Encino Street & Nadeau Street, Los Angeles County., 1905.; 7 items. (Box 112)
- Ninth Street--Boyle to 9th Street Viaduct, Los Angeles., 1926.; 1 item. (Box 133)
- Ninth Street--Downey Rd. to Lorena Street, Los Angeles., 1925.; 1 item. (Box 133)
- Ninth Street--north side, 9th Street and Camulos Street, Los Angeles., 1928.; 1 item. (Box 134)
- Normandie / Carson Street / Vermont, Los Angeles County., 1919.; 1 item. (Box 77)
- Normandie / Fifty-Seventh, Los Angeles County., 1 item. (Box 68)
- North Compton Avenue / Main Street, Los Angeles County., 1920.; 2 items. (Box 79)
- Norton Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1923.; 1 item. (Box 82)
- Obear Tract--San Pedro & 12th Street, Los Angeles., 1908.; 1 item. (Box 125)
- Ocean Park--Venice Canal Subdivision, Los Angeles County., 1906, 1930.; 4 items. (Box 96)
- Ocean Park--Venice Canal Subdivision, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 153)
- Omaha Heights [Huntington Drive], Los Angeles County., 1908.; 1 item. (Box 66)
- Omaha Heights Tract--Lot 12--Mission Road, Los Angeles County., 1905.; 1 item. (Box 117)
- Oneonta Park (Map of Addition no.1), Los Angeles., 1904.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Orange Blossom Colony (Map of), Stanislaus County, California., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Orange Crest Tract--Arlington Avenue & Washington Street, Los Angeles., 1903.; 1 item. (Box 125)
- Pacific Electric Railway, Southern California., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Pacific Inprovement Tract (Map of) of San Pedro, California, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Pacoima Avenue / Ventura County Road, Los Angeles County., 1911.; 1 item. (Box 70)
- Palm Avenue / Strong Ranch (?), Los Angeles County (?)., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 75)
- Palm Garden Courts--Highland Avenue & Sycamore Avenue / Camrose Drive, Los Angeles County., 1928.; 10 items. (Box 78)
- Pasadena--various areas, Los Angeles County., 1920s.; 20 items. (Box 103)
- Pasadena, South Pasadena, Altadena, Glendale, San Gabriel, Alhambra, and Eagle Rock (map by Bekins), Los Angeles., 1 item. (Box 156)
- Penn Tract--Angeleno Avenue & Third Street, Los Angeles County., 1905.; 1 item. (Box 117)
- Phillip's Old Home Tract--Garfield Avenue / Alhambra Road, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Playa Del Rey townsite, Los Angeles County., 1902.; 1 item. (Box 96)
- Pleasant View Heights--Cypress, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 3 items. (Box 134)
- Pleasant View Terrace (Bowen)--Cypress Avenue & Sulfur Street, Los Angeles County., 1906.; 11 items. (Box 114)
- Pomeroy & Mills Subdivision--St. James Street & Sante Fe Railroad Tracks, Los Angeles., 1911.; 1 item. (Box 125)
- Precinct Map of Los Angeles City--Central District, Los Angeles., 1926-1927.; 1 item. (Box 150)
- Precinct Map of Los Angeles City--Harbor District, Los Angeles., 1926-1927.; 1 item. (Box 150)
- Precinct Map of Los Angeles City--San Fernando Valley, Los Angeles., 1926-1927.; 1 item. (Box 150)
- Precinct Map of Los Angeles City--Western District, Los Angeles., 1926-1927.; 1 item. (Box 150)
- Property of the Providencia Land, Water & Development Company showing town of Burbank, Los Angeles County., 1 item. (Box 150)
- Ramona Avenue & Spruce Street, Los Angeles County., 1919.; 4 items. (Box 77)
- Rampart Heights (folder 1 of 2). Los Angeles County., 29 items. (Box 89)
- Rampart Heights (folder 2 of 2), Los Angeles County., 1905, 1925.; 48 items. (Box 90)
- Rampart Heights--Hewes Street Vincent Lot--Coronado Street & 1st Street, Los Angeles., 1907.; 5 items. (Box 128)
- Ramsaur (F.E.) Tract--Central Avenue & Morton Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1903-1920.; 9 items. (Box 127)
- Rancho El Rosario--Tijuana Section, Baja, California., 1926.; 9 items. (Box 104)
- Rancho La Ballona, Los Angeles County., 1893.; 1 item. (Box 124)
- Rancho La Ballona, Los Angeles County., 1868.; 1 item. (Box 139)
- Rancho La Ballona--Candelaria Machado allotment, Los Angeles County., 1912-1913.; 4 items. (Box 104)
- Rancho Los Coyotes, Los Angeles County., 1909.; 4 items. (Box 67)
- Rancho Palos Verdes, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 157)
- Rancho Paso de Bartolo--Plat Map, Southern California., 1881.; 1 item. (Box 138)
- Rancho Paso de Bortolo, Los Angeles., 1913.; 6 items. (Box 74)
- Rancho San Antonio--Los Angeles County Flood Control Map, Los Angeles County., 1915.; 1 item. (Box 137)
- Rancho San Jose de Buenos Ayres, Los Angeles., 1915, 1920.; 15 items. (Box 151)
- Rancho San Jose de Buenos Ayres--including Wolfskill estate, Los Angeles., 1915, 1920.; 23 items. (Box 143)
- Rancho San Jose de Buenos Ayres (folder 1 of 3), Los Angeles., 1915, 1920.; 43 items. (Box 144)
- Rancho San Jose de Buenos Ayres (folder 2 of 3), Los Angeles., 1915, 1920.; 21 items. (Box 145)
- Rancho San Jose de Buenos Ayres (folder 3 of 3), Los Angeles., 1915, 1920.; 24 items. (Box 146)
- Rancho San Rafael / Glassell Road, n.p., 1908.; 1 item. (Box 66)
- Rancho San Vicente y Santa Monica--plat map, Los Angeles County., 1876.; 1 item. (Box 104)
- Rancho San Vincente y Santa Monica--National Boulevard & Sawtelle Boulevard, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 137)
- Rancho Santa Ana del Chino (Map of Subdivision), San Bernardino County., n.d.; 3 items. (Box 156)
- Raymond Park, South Pasadena., 1 item. (Box 156)
- Rendalia Poultry Springs--Santa Ana Avenue & Center Street, Los Angeles County., 1 item. (Box 120)
- Reposado Dr. & Deep Canyon Road, Los Angeles County., 1931.; 2 items. (Box 100)
- Richfield--Placentia-Yorba Boulevard at Adams, Orange County, California., 1928.; 2 items. (Box 137)
- Richmond Canal Sub-Division, Contra Costa County., 2 items. (Box 153)
- Richmond, California, Contra Costa County., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 153)
- Rio Vista Avenue--9th Street to Pitt St., Alosta Street from Soto Street to Pitt Street, Los Angeles., 1927, 1928.; 3 items. (Box 133)
- Rio Vista Avenue--Hollenbeck Avenue to 9th Street, Los Angeles., 1927.; 2 items. (Box 133)
- Rosensteel Place--Alvarado Street & Sixth Street, Los Angeles County., 1897.; 1 item. (Box 114)
- Ross (Dr.) property, Lamanda Park, California., 1 item. (Box 124)
- Rowena Avenue / Ames Street, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 82)
- Royal Tract (Bowen & Chamberlain)--Faneta Street & Figueroa Street, Los Angeles County., 1905.; 2 items. (Box 116)
- San Antonio Ranch & Cerritos Rancho--Downey & Florence Road, Los Angeles County., 1923.; 1 item. (Box 119)
- San Bernardino base meridian--map of south line, San Bernadino County., 1924-1925.; 1 item. (Box 137)
- San Diego County, San Diego County., 1 item. (Box 157)
- San Diego map issued by Bekins, San Diego., 1 item. (Box 156)
- San Diego Street Guide and Automobile Road Map, San Diego., 1 item. (Box 150)
- San Fernando Valley--North Hollywood section, Los Angeles County., 1928.; 2 items. (Box 148)
- San Fernando Valley--Van Nuys Section, Los Angeles., 1 item. (Box 149)
- San Gabriel Boulevard--San Gabriel Boulevard & Garvey Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1907.; 1 item. (Box 136)
- San Gabriel Mission, Los Angeles., 1911.; 1 item. (Box 70)
- San Gabriel Orange Grove Tract--County Road & San Marcos Street, Los Angeles County., 1904.; 1 item. (Box 123)
- San Jacinto & Pleasant Valley Irrigation District--Riverside County Land Company, Riverside County., 1 item. (Box 156)
- San Jacinto Syndicate Lands, Southern California., 1919.; 1 item. (Box 139)
- San Mateo Street & Palora Street--from Zelzah Avenue to Newcastle Avenue, Los Angeles., 1928.; 1 item. (Box 134)
- San Pedro Street Tract (Davenport), Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- San Vicente Boulevard and Santa Monica Canyon--topographical map--7th Street to 17th Street, Santa Monica, California., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 138)
- Sanders (W.S.) Tract--Baugh Road, Los Angeles County., 1906.; 1 item. (Box 128)
- Sanford (George Addison) Allotment--Santa Monica Road, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 129)
- Santa Monica Boulevard--from Pacific Avenue to Aliso Avenue, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 134)
- Santa Monica Boulevard--on the Rancho San Jose de Buenes Aires [Ayres], (?). Los Angeles County., 1916; 1 item. (Box 133)
- Santa Monica Boulevard / Military Avenue, Los Angeles., 1910.; 5 items. (Box 81)
- Santa Monica Land and Water Company--Oil Land on the Wolfskill Road, Los Angeles., 1913.; 1 item. (Box 139)
- Santa Monica unnamed tract--7th Street & Arizona Avenue, Santa Monica, California., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 128)
- Schiller, Mrs. F.C.--house plans--3700 Globe Avenue, Los Angeles [Palms], Los Angeles., 1938.; 78 items. (Box 154)
- Sespie Rancho--Fillmore Subdivision, Ventura County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 150)
- Sewer lines (folder 1 of 2), Los Angeles., 1905, 1932.; 9 items. (Box 140)
- Sewer lines (folder 2 of 2), Los Angeles., 1926-1927.; 8 items. (Box 141)
- Shafer (Caroline & Alice) Tract--Mateo Street & Palmetto Street, Los Angeles., 1891.; 2 items. (Box 114)
- Short Line Subdivision--Venice (folder 1 of 2), Los Angeles County., 1905, 1928.; 26 items. (Box 97)
- Short Line Subdivision--Venice (folder 2 of 2), Los Angeles County., 1904-1905.; 40 items. (Box 98)
- Slauson Junction Tract, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 7 items. (Box 112)
- Slauson Junction Tract--Slauson Avenue & Long Beach Avenue, Los Angeles., 1906.; 2 items. (Box 124)
- Sorrento Tract--Subdivision of Omaha Heights--Huntington Dr, Los Angeles County., 1913.; 5 items. (Box 111)
- Soto Street & Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Line, Los Angeles County., 1926.; 2 items. (Box 100)
- South Cucamonga Town Site--Turner Avenue & Park Street, San Bernadino County, California., 1889.; 1 item. (Box 137)
- South Ocean Park--formerly Short Line Beach, Los Angeles., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 156)
- South West Tract (Strong & Dickinson)--Santa Monica Avenue & Hobart Street, Los Angeles County., 1904.; 2 items. (Box 116)
- Southern Water Company's 20 Pipeline Map--Alameda Street from 6th to 20th Street, Los Angeles., 1905.; 2 items. (Box 139)
- Southgate, California--Los Angeles River at Tweedy Boulevard, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 138)
- Squires (Ella B.) property--Tract 1193 & Tract 1475, Los Angeles County., 1930.; 1 item. (Box 120)
- Standard notice to contractors--City Engineer, Los Angeles., 1927.; 1 item. (Box 148)
- Stocks Tract--Santa Monica Avenue & Normandie Avenue, Los Angeles., 1905.; 1 item. (Box 117)
- Stone Canyon & Los Angeles Avenue, Orange Avenue & Lemon Avenue, Los Angeles County (?)., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 129)
- Stough Ranch--Myrtle Avenue & Sixth Street, Burbank, California., 1907.; 7 items. (Box 136)
- Strong & Dickinson's South West Tract--Santa Monica Avenue & Western Avenue, Los Angeles., 1904.; 1 item. (Box 125)
- Strong (F.R.) Map of the Castle--Mountain Avenue, n.p., 1933, 1939.; 1 item. (Box 139)
- Sunny Slope Estate, Los Angeles County., 1906.; 23 items. (Box 102)
- Sunny Slope Estate--California & Rose Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1906.; 7 items. (Box 129)
- Sunny Slope Estate--California Street, Pasadena., 1937, 1916.; 5 items. (Box 124)
- Sunny Slope Estate--Monte Vista Avenue & San Pasqual Street--Lamanda Park, Pasadena, California., 1 item. (Box 124)
- Sunny Slope Ranch, San Gabriel Valley / Pasadena., n.d.; 7 items. (Box 156)
- Sunny Side no.2 (Grider & Hamilton)--Vermont / 80th Street, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Sunset (?) & Valencia Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1916.; 5 items. (Box 77)
- Sunset Boulevard--Aliso Avenue to Rodi Avenue, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 133)
- Sunset Boulevard--Rancho Rodeo De Las Aguas westerly to Catalina Avenue, Los Angeles., 1907.; 1 item. (Box 132)
- Temple / Micheltorena Street, Los Angeles., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 71)
- Thill, Weber & Brockamp Tract--Moneta Avenue & Vernon Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1904.; 1 item. (Box 110)
- Third Street--Hoover Street to Miami Avenue, Los Angeles., 1906.; 1 item. (Box 132)
- Toland Way / Avenue 45, Los Angeles County., 1920.; 1 item. (Box 79)
- Tujunga Ranch, Los Angeles., 1907.; 1 item. (Box 66)
- Tujunga Road / de Mille Survey, Los Angeles., 1927.; 3 items. (Box 82)
- U.S. Geological Survey maps, Southern California., 1896, 1905.; 38 items. (Box 142)
- Unidentified, fragments, etc, n.p., n.d.; 24 items. (Box 152)
- University addition--Commonwealth Avenue & Geneva Street, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 114)
- Valentine's subdivision (Homestead Tract)--Toberman Street & 16th Street, Los Angeles., 1895.; 1 item. (Box 121)
- Valley View Tract--Sunset Boulevard & Curson Street, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 123)
- Van Nuys (I.N.) tract--between Temple Street & First Street, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Van Nuys section of San Fernando Valley--Payne's Legal Description Map. Los Angeles County., 1 item. (Box 111)
- Venice (City of)--Mildred Avenue / Olive Street, Los Angeles County., 1923.; 2 items. (Box 79)
- Venice--Silver Strand, Los Angeles County., 1905.; 1 item. (Box 96)
- Venice Gateway (M.J. Nolan), Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Venice of America, Los Angeles County., 1904-1905.; 18 items. (Box 95)
- Venice Park, Los Angeles County., 1904, 1923.; 7 items. (Box 96)
- Ventura Boulevard & Encino Avenue, Los Angeles., 1934.; 3 items. (Box 76)
- Ventura Boulevard--Newcastle Avenue to Lindley Avenue, Los Angeles., 1928.; 2 items. (Box 130)
- Ventura Boulevard / Pacoima Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1921.; 1 item. (Box 80)
- Vermont & Ionia, Los Angeles., 1907.; 10 items. (Box 65)
- Vermont Avenue & Rosecrans Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1917.; 1 item. (Box 77)
- Vermont Avenue & School Street, Los Angeles County., 1917.; 1 item. (Box 77)
- Vermont Avenue 120th Street to 135th Street, Los Angeles., 1924.; 1 item. (Box 134)
- Vermont Avenue Villa Tract--between Normandie Avenue & Vermont Avenue, Los Angeles., 1906.; 1 item. (Box 121)
- Vermont Avenue Square, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Vermont Heights--Monte Vista Avenue & Southwest Boulevard Los Angeles County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 153)
- Vernon & Compton Avenue Tract--Compton Avenue & Vernon Avenue, Los Angeles., 1905.; 3 items. (Box 126)
- Vernon & Cooper Avenue Tract--Vernon Avenue & Ascot Avenue, Los Angeles., 1906.; 1 item. (Box 124)
- Vinmont Home Tract / Los Feliz Boulevard Los Angeles County., 1922, 1927.; 5 items. (Box 81)
- Virgil Avenue--1st Street to 3rd Street, Los Angeles., 1906.; 1 item. (Box 131)
- Washington Boulevard / Partenico Street, Los Angeles County., 1926.; 2 items. (Box 78)
- Washington Street--from westerly boundary to Rimpau Avenue, Los Angeles., 1909.; 2 items. (Box 131)
- Washington Street / Hutchinson Street, Los Angeles County., 1925.; 1 item. (Box 84)
- Water Pipeline Brea Valley through Brea Canon to Sante Fe Oil Wells, Los Angeles., 1899.; 2 items. (Box 139)
- Watts, Los Angeles., 1912.; 10 items. (Box 70)
- Watts Subdivision--Licensed Surveyor's Map for Albert H. Beach, Los Angeles., 1929.; 1 item. (Box 153)
- Watts Subdivision--property of Albert H. Beach, Los Angeles., 1926.; 3 items. (Box 106)
- Weiss Tract, McGeary Tract, Estella Tract--Alameda Street & Vejar, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 139)
- West Adams Terrace, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- West Naples, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 153)
- West Washington Street Tract--Washington Street & Western Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1904.; 2 items. (Box 116)
- Western addition to the city of Los Angeles, Los Angeles., 1888.; 1 item. (Box 150)
- Western Heights--Washington Street & Western Street, Los Angeles., 1904.; 1 item. (Box 123)